<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on Attempts by an average programmer</title>
		<link>http://idiotaspirations.com/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on Attempts by an average programmer</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 16:32:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="http://idiotaspirations.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>New Years Resolution</title>
			<link>http://idiotaspirations.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 16:32:39 -0800</pubDate>
			
			<guid>http://idiotaspirations.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
			<description>Self-Improvement; Every year I make New Years resolutions, and I&amp;rsquo;m somewhat successful in holding to them. This year I&amp;rsquo;ve resolved to improve myself by bettering my ability to program. I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m middling in my current ability. I rarely find myself incapable of performing a task, but I&amp;rsquo;d rarely say my solutions are the most optimized or clear to read. On another note, I also struggle to sound professional in emails and other written correspondence and I think writing a devlog would help me in that regards.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="self-improvement">Self-Improvement;</h2>
<p>Every year I make New Years resolutions, and I&rsquo;m somewhat successful in holding to them. This year I&rsquo;ve resolved to improve myself by bettering my ability to program. I&rsquo;d say I&rsquo;m middling in my current ability. I rarely find myself incapable of performing a task, but I&rsquo;d rarely say my solutions are the most optimized or clear to read.
On another note, I also struggle to sound professional in emails and other written correspondence and I think writing a devlog would help me in that regards.
I&rsquo;m currently working through the 2020 Advent of Code to improve my understanding and utilization of Modern C++. I&rsquo;ll be posting my solutions over the course of the next month or so and will likely work through most of 2015-2019 throughout the course of the year.</p>
<div class="highlight"><pre class="chroma"><code class="language-C++" data-lang="C++">    <span class="n">std</span><span class="o">::</span><span class="n">cout</span> <span class="o">&lt;&lt;</span> <span class="s">&#34;Hello, World!&#34;</span> <span class="o">&lt;&lt;</span> <span class="n">std</span><span class="o">::</span><span class="n">endl</span><span class="p">;</span>

</code></pre></div>]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
